SUMMARY

19-year-old, second-year Advanced Computer Science (R&D) student at the Australian National University and Software Developer at CSIRO. I am passionate about software and have been programming from a young age, as a result I have cofounded a software consultancy (Lambda Consulting). This is for the purpose of providing me experience with a variety of technologies and experience working in a team to develop software. I am driven and work hard with little supervision towards my goals; this is evident through my achievements thus far.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Advanced Computing (Research & Development)

2021 - 2024

St Michael's College, Adelaide

2020

South Australian Certificate of Education

- 99.95 ATAR (Highest possible ATAR)
- DUX/Valedictorian of cohort

Australian National University (ANU)

- Attending with National University Scholarship (Awarded for perfect entry score)
- 7.0 GPA (All HD's) with 92% Weighted Average Mark

SKILLS

Languages

- Most Proficient in: Python
- Familiar with: Java, Haskell, Dart, JavaScript (node.js)

Frameworks/Software

Backend: Flask, SQL

Frontend: React (Web), Flutter (Mobile)

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

August 2021 - Present

CSIRO

- Developed, tested, and deployed a data-processing pipeline which derives certain hydrological properties of the Murray Darling Basin (largest river system in Australia).
- This project was completed using Python and taught me the applications of many text-book algorithms and data structures.
- Due to the scale of the computation the pipeline has been written such that it is distributed on AWS compute using DASK.

Software Consultant October 2021 - Present

Lambda Consulting (https://lambdaconsulting.com.au)

- Co-founded this business with friends with the aim of gaining experience in working alongside a customer to develop software solutions and to meet requirements.
- Working on our first contract, being a loyalty promotional app for a large bar in Canberra, Australia.

Software Developer March 2021 - Present

ANU Rocketry

Designed and managed the development of a new control system for the propulsion sub-team.

PROJECTS MORE: <u>HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/PSTEFA1707</u>

5th Avenue Bar Membership App (Full stack - Python, Dart (Flutter), SQL, React.Js)

2021

- Membership and rewards app (Android & iOS) integrating with Square POS for a bar in Canberra.
- Currently in development, I am working across the full stack.

Case Law Search Engine (Full stack - Python, PyTorch, React.Js)

2021

- Worked on a natural language search website for legal cases in a team of 5.
- Made design decisions, implemented database infrastructure, and worked to scrape tens of thousands of cases along with metadata to produce training data for a BERT based Al model.
- Implemented Google's PageRank algorithm on the citations within cases to assist in ordering cases by relevancy.

Rocket Control System (Full stack - Python, JavaScript, React.Js)

2021

- Upon joining the ANU Rocketry team I realized the software that was being used was subpar and unreliable. I then designed
 and managed the development of a new control system.
- This control system operates wirelessly, contains error handling and reporting, logging, sequencing, and visualizes sensor readings.

WhitelistPy Discord Bot (Python, SQL, AWS EC2)

2022

- Developed a discord bot to manage whitelisting for NFT releases. Is now running on over 100 servers handling thousands of requests.
- Used by the following projects: https://twitter.com/DuckFrens

AWARDS

South Australian Governor's Commendation – Academic Excellence Award South Australian Certificate of Education Subject Merit (x5) DUX of St Michael's College

2021

0000

2020

National Computer Science School Programming Challenge (NCSS) Top 1%

2019